海莉 快点
Haley, hurry up!
你快来不及了 我还做了巧克力煎饼
You don't have much time, and I made chocolate chip pancakes.
老妈 我不是12岁的小孩了
Mom, I'm not 12.
她那份给我
Dibs on hers.
宝贝 第一天上班激动吗
Honey, you excited about your first day?
你猜怎么着 我真的很激动
You know what? I really am.
上班这事儿吧
There's something about going to work
会让人觉得自己
that makes you feel like you're...
不知道 有价值吧
I don't know, worth something.
别介意哈 老妈
No offense, mom.
听着 我想给你一些建议
Listen... I wanna give you some advice.
快点说 她要迟到了
Do it fast. She's gonna be late.
努力工作
Work hard.
专心致志
Keep your eye on the ball.
注意力集中
Stay focused.
永不...快看
Never... check it out!
小卡穿着工装
Cam in overalls!
米奇尔也给我发了一张
Mitchell sent me the same text!
为什么写着"瞧你干了什么好事"
Why "Look what you've done"?
因为小卡要来帮我
Oh, because Cam is helping me out
建一个棒球场
with that baseball field,
但米奇尔讨厌他打扮得跟农民似的
and Mitchell hates it when he gets all farmed up.
一提到农场和菲茨宝小丑 他就郁闷
His turn-offs are farm, Fizbo,
最郁闷的就是 农场宝
And, worst of all, farmbo.
你好呀 我的伙计
Howdy, life pardner!
我得走了 我不想第一天就迟...
Well, I gotta go. Don't wanna be late for my first--
天呐 你们怎么没告诉我时间
Oh, my god! Why didn't you guys tell me the time?!
你觉得怎么样 我们能把这改造成棒球场吗
So what do you think? Can we turn this into a baseball field?
当然 没有问题
Oh, yeah. No problem.
以前在农场
You know, back on the farm,
我曾把一英亩的玉米地改造成了雪花形迷宫
I once turned an acre of corn into a snowflake-shaped maze.
要不是邻居比利·鲍勃·希恩伯格
It'd still be there if our neighbor Billy Bob Sheinberg
从他的撒药飞机上看下去
hadn't seen it from his crop duster
说像纳粹卐字标 迷宫肯定还保留着
and said it looked like a swastika.
卢克的球队表现怎么样啊
So how good's Luke's team anyway?
你可以上Youtube搜
Well, you may have seen them on youtube
"男孩卡在头盔里了"
under "Boy stuck in batting helmet"
或者"投球手击中自己的头部"
or "Pitcher beans self."
不过其中一些孩子今年提早进入了青春期
But a few of them went through puberty early this year, so...
他们说是牛奶中的激素所致
They say it's because of hormones in our milk.
但不管是什么 确实挺管用的
But whatever it is, they really jacked up.
卢克和曼尼的球队要争取季后赛的最后一席
Luke and Manny's team tied for the final spot in the playoffs,
但由于没人料到如此
but since nobody was expecting it,
想订球场时已经来不及了
all the fields were booked.
对手球队想要抛硬币来一决胜负
The other team wanted to settle with a coin flip.
但我们说要石头剪刀布 于是就谈崩了
We said "Rock paper scissors." That's when talks broke down.
找不到球场该怎么办呢
So what do you do when you can't find a field?
自己建一个
You build one.
于是我们笑到了最后
And we got the last laugh,
因为你猜我找到了什么
'cause guess what I found there?
石头 剪刀 和布
Rocks, paper, and scissors.
-我觉得本垒该设在这儿 -嗯
- I see home plate up here. - Mm-hmm.
投手区在那儿
I see pitcher's mound in here,
于是小男孩的梦想就此成真了
And I see little boys' dreams coming true everywhere.
我发现了一条死蛇
I found a dead snake!
真是"好"啊
It's perfect.
没死 没死
Not dead! Not dead!
我要当上年度"好母亲"了
I'm gonna be mother of the year.
这里是我们的餐厅 我们吃饭的地方
And this is our dining room, where we eat.
这里是我们的厨房 也是吃饭的地方
And this is our kitchen, where we also eat.
你在跟谁说话
Who are you talking to?
看起来像是你跟旅行团走散了
It looks like you lost your tour.
或是精神失常了
Or your mind.
我在跟宝宝讲话
The baby.
小短的女朋友达琳送给我的
Shorty's girlfriend Darlene send it to me.
她说有利于产前母子关系的培养
She said it's for prenatal bonding.
我爱死了 我们参观了我们的家
I love it. We took a tour of the house.
还看了我所有的鞋子
We took a look at all my shoes.
来吧 杰 跟宝宝说说话
Come on, Jay. Say something to the baby.
达琳是个傻瓜
Darlene's an idiot.
好吧 太棒了
Oh, yeah, beautiful.
你对宝宝说的第一句话就是
Your first words to our baby--
达琳是个傻瓜
"Darlene is an idiot."
太愚蠢了 宝宝就隔着肚皮
This is stupid. The baby's only 2 inches away.
要跟他讲话 根本不用拿着麦克风吼
He doesn't need speakers blasting at him.
就像如今的餐厅
Like in restaurants nowadays
你根本听不到自己在想什么
where you can't even hear yourself think.
反正你爱干嘛就干嘛 我操个什么心
Ah, you're gonna do whatever you want. Why do I bother?
习惯就好 有时候你就得让他发泄下
Get used to that. Sometimes you just gotta let him go.
他会吃点冰冻果子露 睡一觉
Then he eats some sherbet and falls asleep.
我要用这玩意儿在场地上划线
Okay, I'll chalk the field with this bad boy.
你划线时 我来搞定垒位
And while you're doing that, I will get the bases.
我们真是默契
We make such a good team.
为什么你的朋友会有粉笔划线车
Why does your friend have a chalker?
他用来求婚的 那人是开飞机在空中作画的
Oh, he used it to propose to a skywriter.
女士 女士 需要我帮忙吗
Oh, ma'am? Ma'am, do you need help with that?
是的 拜托了
Oh, yes. Please.
这是你的房子吗
Is this your house?
我要搬去和我的儿子一起住
I'm moving in with my son.
他很有钱
He's rich.
马桶边都装了电话
Phone by the toilet rich.
那你在这儿住很久了吗
All right, so have you lived here a long time?
我是62年搬过来 想做演员的
I moved here in '62 to be an actress.
我在《洛克福档案》一剧中有句台词
I had one line in a "Rockford files."
他从后门溜走了
"He went out the back.,"
谁从后门溜走了
Who went out the back?
原来那是你演的啊
That was you.
这个给你弄好了
Well, you're all set here.
你们对这房子有兴趣吗
You're not interested in the place, are you?
-没有 谢谢 -有 我们有兴趣
- Oh, no, thank you. - Yes--yes, we are.
是的是的 我们有兴趣
Yes. Yes, we are.
-过来吧 -好的
- Come on. - Okay.
眼睛不能闭上
You gotta keep your eyes open.
球快打中脸了 闭眼是正常反应啊
It's not natural when a ball is hurtling at your face.
你能往球棒中间握一点吗[激动地说不出话]
Will you choke up a little?
那得等到奏国歌的时候
Probably when they play the national anthem.
不 我是说 你的手往上握一点
No, move your hands up the bat.
得等到奏国歌的时候
"When they play the national anthem."
我有着完美的纪录
I had a perfect record--
22场比赛 我一局都没上
22 games, and I hadn't played a single inning.
然后麦考伊双胞胎的奶奶死了
Then the Mccoy twins' grandma dies,
我就被突然叫上右外场
and suddenly I'm starting at right field.
那到底什么意思啊 跟舞台右侧一样吗
What does that even mean? Is it the same as stage right?
准备好了吗 慢慢来 放轻松
All right, ready? Nice and easy.
我都还没扔呢
I haven't even thrown it yet.
那是你的错 我做了我该做的事
Then it's your fault. I'm doing my part.
算了吧 我们得采取新措施
Forget it. We need to do something different.
你的击球姿势要改一改
Let's change your stance.
试着往前倾一点
Try leaning in.
再倾斜一点
Further.
现在闭上眼睛
Now close your eyes.
好极了 你可以每次都这样吗
Ah! Perfect! You think you can do that every time?
哪样 故意挨打吗
What, get hit on purpose?
你想上垒成为英雄就得这样
If you wanna get on base and be a hero.
有些人生而伟大
Some men are born into greatness.
有些人活该丢脸
Others have it chucked at their face.
真棒
Yes!
布鲁克太太 非常感谢
Okay, Mrs. Brooks, thank you very much.
我们会尽快跟你联系的
We'll be in touch very soon.
再说一次
Say it one more time.
他从后门溜走了
He went out the back.
-我喜欢 大爱啊 -精彩 精彩
- Oh, love it! Love it! - Brava! Brava!
再见
Bye-bye!
菲尔 你觉得怎么样
What do you think, Phil?
不得不承认 真是遇着个大便宜
Well, I have to admit, it's a steal.
没错啊 我就说嘛
Yes! Yes! I told you!
你还说吉尔·索普靠炒房赚了一大笔钱
And you said Gil Thorpe makes a killing flipping houses.
可不 他一直拿这件事大吹特吹
Yeah, he brags about it all the time.
他每做成一笔买卖
Every time he makes a sale,
都说自己是"大炒家"
he calls himself "Flipper"
一边走来走去一边发海豚音 像这样...
And walks around making this dolphin sound. Like...
他是怎么发出来的 我真讨厌他
How does he do it? I hate him so much.
要是我们四个一起合伙
Okay, look, if the four of us go in on this together,
就能把风险降到最低
We can minimize the risk.
或者我们谁都别掺和
Or if none of us do it,
就能完全避免风险
we can eliminate the risk altogether
因为你们都对翻新旧房投资一无所知
because none of you know anything about flipping houses.
我们都已经想好了
Okay, well, we already have it figured out.
由我来担任设计师
I'm gonna be the designer...
因为我熟知颜色和图形
Because I know about colors and shapes.
没错 莉莉也知道
Yeah, so does Lily.
我来担任承建人
I'm gonna be the contractor.
那我来当宇航员 真好玩 菲尔 你来
And I'm gonna be the astronaut. Oh, this is fun. Phil, you go.
米奇尔 我说正经的
Mitchell, I am serious.
我给自己家很多工程当过监工
I have overseen lots of projects in our home.
我家浴室改造就是我监工的
I oversaw the remodel of our bathroom.
没超预算 对不对 菲尔
Under budget. Right, Phil?
没错 我有点儿失望没装
Yeah. I was a little disappointed we didn't go for
有自动冲屁屁功能的马桶 其它的...
the butt-washing toilet, but otherwise...
你自己洗屁股又不用花钱
You can wash your own butt for free.
那不一样 好吗
Well, that's not the same, is it?
我很高兴谈这个
This is all fun to talk about.
真的 但是我想你们还是没弄明白
It is, but I don't think that you understand
炒房意味着什么 而且...
what--what this could really entail. And--
好了 米奇尔说"不" 我们就死心吧
Okay, there it is. Mitchell just said "No," So we're done.
意外吗 不意外
Surprise, surprise.
我们回家再谈 好吗
Listen, we'll talk about this at home, okay?
别灰心
Don't give up.
菲尔 你也同意这是个好主意吧
Phil, you think it's a good idea, right?
绝对的
Totally.
对 而且你也觉得我们能应付得来 对吧
Yes. And you know we can handle it, right?
我认为你们什么都能应付
I think you guys can handle anything.
那你过去跟他谈谈 你可是专业人士
And you go talk to him. You're a professional.
他会尊重你的意见
He respects you.
好吧 让我们单聊 我和他好好谈谈
Okay. Give us some space. I'll go talk him into it.
-好的 -好吗
- All right. - All right?
-好的 -好
- Okay. - Okay.
听着
Listen...
我们绝对不能让他们干这件事
there's no way we're letting them do this.
我就说嘛 是不是
I know, right?
他们那两把刷子根本搞不定
They are not equipped to take this on.
我们所有的积蓄都会随我家那无趣的
We might as well flush all our savings
旧马桶一冲而逝的
down my boring old toilet.
你真的很纠结马桶的事啊
Oh, you are really bitter about that.
当时我就这要求 别把你的太阳镜坐碎了
It's the one thing I asked for. Don't sit on your sunglasses.
很遗憾 伙计们
Sorry, guys.
哎呀 说得再明白一点
Whoops. Just to be clear, though.
无论如何 我们都不能让他们做这件事
Under no circumstances are we letting them do this?
我完全同意
I am totally with you.
你待在这边 我去传达坏消息
Okay, you stay here. I'll go break the bad news.
对不起 伙计们 没说动他
Sorry, guys. Not gonna happen.
-可是 要不我... -放弃吧
- Yeah, well, maybe if-- - I would drop it.
不值得为这个吵架 来 克莱尔
It's not worth the fight. Come on, Claire.
我们走的越快 伤的越轻
The faster we leave, the less it's gonna hurt.
上车
Hop in. Yep.
为什么非得这样呢
Why does it have to be like this?
不知道呀 你弟弟 系上安全带没 好
I don't know. He's your brother. Buckled up? Good.
别 别走 我明白你的阴招了
No! No! No, no, I see what you're doing!
他也不赞成
He doesn't want this either!
-放点儿音乐 -好的
- Little radio? - Sure.
菲尔 克莱尔
Phil! Claire!
拜托
Come on!
真可惜
It's such a shame
因为我知道我们一定会把那房子炒成功的
because I know we would do a great job on that house.
-当然 -吉尔·索普能做我就能做 对吧
- Totally. - If Gil Thorpe can do it, I can do it, right?
拜托
Please!
拜托 吉尔·索普有几十年的经验
Please. Gil Thorpe has decades of experience
以及一向靠谱的直觉
and infallible instincts.
虽说人人都希望不是这样子的
As much as we'd all like to believe otherwise,
但我娶的可不是吉尔·索普
I did not marry Gil Thorpe.
你能想象吗
Can you imagine that?
老天爷 那我们得卖出去老多房子了
God, we'd sell a lot of houses.
太好了
Oh! Great.
-是米奇尔 -你知道吗 克莱尔
- Mitchell. - Oh, you know what, Claire?
你得冷静下 不然会把事情搞得更糟
You gotta cool down or you're just gonna make this worse.
你还是去买咖啡吧
Why don't you go get the coffees?
我和他交涉
And I'll deal with him.
好吧 你要和他说什么
Well, okay, what are you gonna say to him?
我要和他来一场男人间的对话
I'm just gonna talk to him man-to-man.
好吧
Right.
好
Okay.
喂
Hello?
克莱尔 菲尔也不愿意买那栋房子
Claire, Phil doesn't want the house either, all right?
他就是让我替他受过 他是个骗子
He's letting me take the fall. He's a liar.
而且是个聪明的骗子
And a clever one.
你以为你能瞒她多久
Ugh! How long do you think you can keep this from her?
到最后我还是会和她说的
All right? I'm gonna talk to her eventually.
那既然我们一直互吐心声
Well, as long as we're swapping stories,
或许我该跟小卡说说
Maybe I'll tell Cam
他给你织的那件毛衣到底是什么下场
What happened to the sweater he knit for you.
不行
I can't.
不行 受不了了
I can't! I can't!
我受不了了 我得把这个傻玩意儿扔了
I can't do it! I can't take this stupid thing anymore!
它是被人从车里偷走的 你明白没
It was stolen out of the car. Do you understand me?
懂了
Got it.
真卑鄙
That is low.
我知道 别生我气
I know. Don't be mad at me.
所以说 我劝你别再打了
That said, I suggest you lose this number.
我并不为自己的行为感到骄傲
I'm not proud of what I did,
但我不是那种摧毁别人梦想的人
but I'm not comfortable squashing people's dreams.
我可是个啦啦队长
I am a cheerleader.
我习惯于在叠罗汉最高处大喊
I'm the guy on top of the pyramid shouting,
朝着梦想 加油
"Go, dreams, go!"
知道什么话不能加油吗
You know what's not a cheer?
二 四 六 八
"Two, four, six, eight,
你会搞砸它
you are going to fail at this
害我们卖铁又砸锅 克莱尔
and lose everything we've worked for, Claire!
*别出声 小宝贝*
*Hush, little baby,*
*你什么都不用说*
*don't say a word.*
*爸爸会给你买只知更鸟*
*Papa's going to buy you a mockingbird.*
*要是那只知更鸟不唱歌*
*And if that mockingbird won't sing,*
*爸爸就给你买只大钻戒*
*papa's gonna buy you a diamond ring.*
爸爸愿意出钱买十只钻戒
Papa'd buy ten diamond rings
让那只呱噪的知更鸟闭上嘴
to get that mockingbird to shut the hell up.
但我不会跟歌洛莉亚说她唱歌难听
But I wasn't gonna tell Gloria she was a terrible singer.
那简直是自掘坟墓
That's just taking a bath with a toaster.
但是 一想到
Still, the thought of
我可怜的小宝贝像个人质一样被困在里面
that poor little thing stuck in there like a hostage,
被迫全天候听着那样的噪音
listening to that racket days on end...
让我于心何忍
I just couldn't take it.
*要是那只公山羊不使劲*
*And if that billy goat won't push,*
*爸爸会给你...*
*papa's gonna get every le--*
我来告诉你爸爸会怎么样
I'll tell you what papa's gonna do.
他会接过这只麦克风
He's gonna take a turn on that mic.
-真的吗 -是的 我一直在想
- Oh! Really? - Yeah, I've been thinking,
这是建立感情的机会 我也该试试
if it's a chance to bond, I should take it.
杰 太好了
Ay, Jay, that's great.
我觉得宝宝不应该
I think that the sound of my voice
只听到我一个人的声音
shouldn't be the only thing that the baby should hear.
完全同意
Same page.
呼叫 呼叫 我是老杰
Breaker, breaker, big Jay.
宝宝 你在什么方位 完毕
Baby, what's your 20? Over.
好萌啊你
Ay, that's so cute.
听起来像电影《警察与卡车强盗》中的对话
You sound like Smokey and the Bandito.
继续继续
Go on. Go on.
你好 孩子 我是你爸杰·普里契特
Hi, kid. This is your dad Jay Pritchett.
我们都迫不及待想见到你
Uh, we're all pretty excited to meet you.
就给你提个醒
Just a heads-up--
我可能比你想象的要老一点
I might be a few years older than you're expecting.
但好的方面是 我们的日子过得很滋润
But on the plus side, we're very comfortable.
什么 没反应吗
What's that? Nothin'?
难逗乐的宝宝
Tough womb.
你在里面干什么呢 睡觉吗
What are you doing in there? You sleepin'?
*你在睡觉吗*
*Are you sleeping?*
-停停停 -*你在...*
- Ah! Ah! Ah! - *Are you--*
爸爸还没说完呢
Ah! Still daddy's turn.
该死 该死的石头
Dumb--dumb rock!
-你是哭了吗 -没有
- Are you cryin'? - No.
没有 我只是弄不走这块石头
No. I just can't get this rock to budge.
从《红粉联盟》里我们学到了什么
Okay, what did we learn from "A League of Their Own"?
棒球场上不能掉眼泪
No crying in baseball.
错 我们知道了麦当娜演技很差
No. That Madonna's a lousy actress,
你也一样
and so are you.
你到底怎么了
What's really going on?
好吧
Okay.
你知道吗 几个月以来
You know, over the last couple of months,
我申请了五份工作
I've applied for, like, five different jobs.
-我还真不知道 -我跟谁也没说
- I didn't know that. - No. I didn't tell anyone,
因为没一家愿意要我的 小卡
Because I didn't get them, Cam.
我上过大学的 你知道吗
I went to college, you know?
我只是想赚钱供孩子们上学
And... I just wanna be able to contribute to my kids' education.
我还想给我老公买件礼物
And I wanna be able to buy my husband a present...
用我自己的钱买
with my own money.
你不用说我也明白
Hey, you're preaching to the choir director.
这正是我成为唱诗班指导的原因
It's actually why I became a choir director.
你在公立学校兼职教书是为了赚钱吗
You became a part-time teacher in a public school for money?
我比你挣得多
I make more than you do.
我是说 不算停车费的话 但是
I mean, before parking. But...
我很抱歉米奇尔扼杀了我们的炒房梦
Look, I'm sorry Mitchell killed our house dream.
尤其是现在我知道你挣钱是为了
You know, now especially that I know you wanted to use the money
去做那么高尚的事
for such noble reasons.
是啊
Yeah.
另外...
And also...
有一双我超想买的靴子
there was this pair of boots.
谁没有想买的靴子啊
There's always a pair of boots.
米奇尔 你知道我意识到什么了吗
Mitchell, do you know what I've realized?
有些事还是不说为妙吗
That some thoughts are better left unexpressed?
不 我意识到在这段感情中
No. That in this relationship,
我是油门 而你是刹车
I'm the gas pedal, and you're the brakes.
慢着 慢着慢着
Okay, wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
上星期你还说
Last week, you said that
你是画儿我是框呢
you were the painting and I was the frame.
那是把我们比喻成艺术品
That's if we were artwork.
现在我把我们比喻成一辆车
This is if we were a car.
要是比喻成马的话 我知道你是哪部分
I know what part you'd be if we were a horse.
-你说什么 -什么
- Excuse me? - Hmm?
我和克莱尔给你带来一个好机会
Claire and I bring you this great opportunity,
你却无情地拒绝了
And you stop it cold.
你不是刹车是什么
I guess that's what brakes do.
你知道刹车还有什么作用吗
You know what brakes also do?
能避免你冲下悬崖
They keep you from driving off cliffs.
也许根本就不存在悬崖 也许是个上坡
Maybe they're not cliffs. Maybe they're ramps,
能把我们带向崭新的美好未来
ready to launch us into new, exciting vistas.
不只我一人反对这投资房子的事
I am not the only one against this whole house thing.
菲尔也不同意
Phil doesn't want it either.
你一直这么说
You keep saying that,
但我非常 非常怀疑
but I find that very, very hard to believe.
菲尔总是支持克莱尔
Phil supports Claire.
他是个充满正能量的啦啦队长
Phil is a cheerleader.
你怎么就不能学学菲尔呢
Why can't you be more like phil?
就在那时我猛然想到
And then it hit me.
我可以学学菲尔
I could be exactly like Phil.
我可以假装支持他们
I could pretend to be on board,
让啦啦队长来背黑锅
forcing the cheerleader to be the bad guy.
我知道这么做挺卑鄙
I know it's underhanded,
但爷就是这么卑鄙
but that's the way I throw.
-米奇尔 -你猜怎么着
- Mitchell? - You--you know what?
我被你说服了
You've convinced me.
如果你和克莱尔 还有尤其是菲尔
If--if you and Claire and especially Phil
想这么干 那我支持你们
are into this, then I'm on board.
-什么 真的吗 -对 全力支持
- What? Seriously?! - Yes! 100%.
实际上 你何不这就打给克莱尔和菲尔
In fact, why don't you call Claire and Phil
告诉他们这个好消息
right now and tell them?
好 通往未来的上坡打动你了对吗
Okay. It was the ramp thing, wasn't it?
我也真心觉得这句很有感染力
You know, I felt really good about it.
什么
What?
真的吗 太好了
Are you serious? That's fantastic!
我得告诉菲尔 马上给你打回去
Oh! I gotta tell Phil. I'll call you right back.
怎么 什么事
What's--what's up?
米奇尔改主意了
Mitchell changed his mind.
他愿意加入 我们要投资房地产咯
He's all for it. We're flipping a house!
-好耶 -好耶
- Yeah. - Yeah!
喂 你好啊 菲尔
Well, hello, Phil.
接到你的电话真是倍感荣幸啊
To what do I owe this pleasure?
少装蒜了
Cut the crap.
想扮无辜吗 那可是我的专长
You wanna play chicken? Chicken's my middle name.
听不懂你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我只是在支持我的伴侣及姐姐
I'm just being supportive of my partner and my sister,
我非常爱他们两个
both of whom I love very much.
做这种缺德事你晚上睡得着吗
How do you sleep at night?
睡得可香了 我知道你会主持大义的
Soundly, knowing you'll do the right thing.
菲尔 怎么样
So how about it, Phil?
你能力挽狂澜吗 刹车已经不灵了
You gonna stop this train? 'cause these brakes are out.
哦对了 我劝你别再打了
Oh. And I suggest you lose this number.
米奇尔
Mitchell?
Mitchell?!
是的 老子怒了
Yeah, I was pretty ticked off
米奇尔居然在我的计上耍计
that Mitchell double-crossed my double-cross.
他现在不接我电话
And then he stopped taking my calls,
所以我谨慎地遣词造句 发给他如下短信
And so I sent him the following carefully worded text...
你坏透了
"U suck."
我知道菲尔受了伤
I could tell Phil felt pretty hurt
心里憋屈 所以我给了如下回复
and betrayed, so I responded.
你打算如何加油杀出一条血路 啦啦队长
"How r u gonna cheerlead your way out of this one, buffy?"
我们都知道买房子这事是场灾难
"We both know this house thing is a disaster."
那你就出声 否则我来
"Then say something, or I will.
我不介意你向小卡揭发...
I don't care if you tell Cam..."
我把那件丑陋的毛衣扔了
"I threw out that hideous sweater?!"
我用数月织了那件"丑陋"的毛衣
I spent months knitting that hideous sweater.
-是吧 -我们怎么能看到短信
- Yeah. - W--how are we seeing this?
他俩昨天就开始用群短信了
They're using the group text from yesterday.
他们根本不知道我会看到
They have no idea these are even coming to me.
好吧
Okay.
又来一条
Oh. Here's another one.
我们得想办法神不知鬼不觉地
"We need to shut this house thing down
让买房这事儿泡汤
Without them knowing it's us"?!
有种啊你们
Oh! Well...
太迟了
"2 late."
完了 这下糟了
No, that--that's bad.
克莱尔 我错了
Claire, I am so sorry.
我不应该对你隐瞒的 但是我...
I know I should've been more honest with you, but I--
不 菲尔
No, Phil.
知道最让我伤心的是什么
You know what really kills me?
你信什么也不信我
Is you didn't believe in me, and you believe in everything!
我就知道那件毛衣不是被人偷了
You know, I knew that sweater wasn't stolen.
亏我特地选了蓝色毛线来衬你的蓝眼睛
And here I pick blue yarn to match your eyes,
我应该选黑色的来搭你的心
but I should've picked black to match your heart.
不过你穿黑色真心帅 你妹的
Although you look amazing in black. Damn you.
我们走
Come on.
17人死亡 数千居民没有供电
"...Leaving 17 dead and thousands without power."
杰 拜托
Ay, Jay, please!
让宝宝听这么恐怖的东西不好
It's bad that the baby listens to such terrible things.
他听过更恐怖的
He's heard worse.
杰 你知道哪有好的一小时即取干洗店吗
Jay, do you know a good 1-hour dry cleaner?
不是"十点前收
And I don't mean the "Must be in by 10:00,
仅工作日营业 且凭优惠券使用"那种
only on weekdays, you need a coupon" Kind.
就是实打实的一小时
I mean a hard 1-hour.
这段对话感觉有实打实的一小时
This conversation feels like a hard one hour.
你去干洗店干嘛 这挺干净的啊
And what do you need it cleaned for? It's spotless.
被罗本的三明治溅上芥末酱了
There's mustard here from Reuben's reuben.
让个自恋狂负责零食日
That's what happens when
就会落得这个下场
you put a narcissist in charge of snack day.
好啦 又该我了
Okay, it's my turn again.
宝贝 又到妈妈咯
Baby, it's your mother again.
-我... -歌洛莉亚
- I'm-- - Gloria?
何不让他休息片刻
Why don't we give him a break?
也许他需要休息一下
He probably needs a minute
毕竟他刚听了致命龙卷风的故事
because he just learned about a deadly tornado.
行 但别一直用"他"称呼宝宝
Okay, stop calling him a he.
如果是个女孩儿呢 你会让她生气的
What if he's a she, and you're making her upset?
我跟你说过 这不为了方便点嘛
I told you. That's just the shorthand I'm using.
-别总挑我刺儿啦 -是吗
- Don't jump down my throat every time I'm - Ay, yes,
-那是因为你总是... -你们干嘛呢
- because you always - What are you doing?
你们想让肚子里的宝宝
Do you really want your unborn baby
听见你们的争吵吗
to hear you fighting like this?
研究表明置胎儿
Studies show it's unhealthy
于紧张氛围下 会有害其健康
For a fetus to be exposed to a stressful environment.
刚13岁谈什么研究 去看漫画书去
Studies? You're 13. Read a comic book.
你那比赛几点开始
What time does your game start?
我得三点钟到 先做"打"球练习
I have to be there at 3:00 for hitting practice.
那叫击球练习
Batting practice.
打中的是我
Not for me.
杰 我不想让宝宝认为
Jay, I don't want our baby to think
他将出生在一个不和睦的家庭
that it's coming into an unhappy home.
我们得保证 永远不会再在他面前吵架了
Let's promise that we're never ever going to fight in front of him.
不在宝宝面前吵架
No fighting in front of the baby.
对 很好
Okay, good.
*一闪一闪*
*Twinkle, twinkle*
*小羊羔啊*
*Little lamb*
歌洛莉亚 别再唱了
Gloria, stop it! Stop it. No more singing.
为什么
Why?
你唱得太烂了
Because you stink.
你真的不会唱歌
You're a terrible singer.
来 我们该吃午饭了
Come on. Let's get some lunch.
你胆敢说我...
How dare do you say that I am...
我了解 别这样
I know! Ay, no, no, no.
刚说好的 不在宝宝面前吵架
No fighting in front of the baby. We just made a deal.
但那不公平
Yeah, but that's not fair
我一直都跟宝宝在一起
because I am always in front of the baby!
歌洛莉亚 作为一个女人你接近完美
Gloria, you're as close to perfect as woman gets.
有点小瑕疵也没什么嘛
Nothing wrong with one tiny, little flaw.
就是你唱歌的时候
Yours is when you start to sing,
声音有如吸尘器被什么东西卡住了
is sounds like something got stuck in the vacuum cleaner.
那是你...
That's--you're just--
别这样
No, no, no.
那只是你不懂欣赏罢了 杰
That is just your stupid, stupid opinion, Jay.
我现在很生气
But I am very angry at you,
我会去列个单
and I am gonna make a list
把生下宝宝后立马就会冲你大吼的
of all the things that I am going to scream at you
所有事儿都写下来
as soon as this baby's out of me.
我没想到她会攒着到将来报复
I didn't think it all the way through.
你好 米奇
Oh, hello, Mitch.
你居然给克莱尔买花
Uh, you got Claire flowers?
嗯 昨晚够难熬的
Yes. I had a little bit of a rough night.
我何尝不是
Yeah, you and me both.
爸爸昨天睡我屋来着
Daddy slept in my room last night.
-分给我点儿 -搞什么 不行
- Here, give me some of those. - What? No.
-都是你害我的 -别拽了 弄坏了
- You got me into this. - Hey, stop! You're breaking them!
我不能空着手见小卡
I need--I'm not going to Cam empty-handed!
菲尔 快松手
Phil, let go of the...
稳住
Hold still!
这全是克莱尔与小卡的功劳吗
Claire and Cam did all this?
一周前 这里还是一片废墟
A week ago, that was all junk.
太不可思议了
It's amazing.
中间有些不平坦
I mean, there's that little bump in the middle.
但除此之外...
But other than that...
就算哪个小家伙打出了五个全垒打
Even if one of those boys had hit five home runs,
赛场上最耀眼的明星依然是克莱尔
the biggest star on that field was Claire.
这就是婚姻的可笑之处
That's the funny thing about marriage.
你爱上了一个
You fall in love with this...
卓越优秀的人
extraordinary person,
但随着时间推移 却只能看到对方的平凡
And over time, they begin to seem ordinary.
我觉得是她太唠叨的缘故
I think it's all the nagging.
哇 这真是
Wow. This...
这真是太不可思议了
This is incredible.
你真是有一双识钻石的慧眼
You literally saw a diamond in the rough.
是 我承担了很多没人愿意承担的项目
Yeah, but I take on a lot of projects no one else is willing to.
是我活该
I deserve that.
我是个白痴居然质疑你的能力
I was an idiot for doubting you.
亲爱的 求你原谅我
Please, honey, forgive me.
看在你送我
How could I not,
这束烂花的份上 我怎能不原谅
when you give me this bouquet of crumpled flowers?
-都怪米奇尔 -又赖他吗
- Mitchell did that! - Mitchell again?
不信问莉莉啊
Ask Lily!
-小卡 -来啦
- Hey, Cam. - Hey.
给你 拿着
Here you--Okay. Well...
哇 支离破碎
Oh, wow. Broken and mangled...
和人家的小心脏一样
Just like my heart.
小卡 对不起我没有支持你
Cam, I'm sorry for not supporting you.
-那毛衣呢 -不可原谅
- What about the sweater? - That's unforgivable.
你花费了那么多心思和时间
I mean, you put all that time and work into it,
我就那样从车窗扔出去了
and I just toss it out the car window.
从车窗扔出去了
Tossed it out the car window?!
不小心坦白过头了
I'm forgetting how much you knew.
知道吗 伙计们 说实话
You know what, guys? Honestly, I...
我觉得我们应该行动 投资那栋房子
I think we should do it. I think we should go for the house.
-真的吗 -谨慎些 亲爱的
- Really? - Okay, but careful, honey.
不是真心话不要说出来
Don't say something if you don't mean it.
我是真心的 我觉得你俩太厉害了
No, I do mean it. I think you two will do a fantastic job.
我也这样觉得 我入伙了
You know, I do, too. I'm on board.
入什么伙
On board for what?
我们四个 打算投资房子
Oh, well, the four of us, uh, might go in on a house.
克莱尔和我负责翻新工作
Claire and I fix it up and flip it.
那是我听过的最糟糕的主意
That's the worst idea I ever heard.
你们对建筑一窍不通
You guys know nothing about construction.
你们会犯下各种错误
You'll make all sorts of mistakes,
你们会反目 不再理会对方
you'll turn on each other, you'll stop talking,
突然间 周末聚餐由一次变成两次
and suddenly I'm doing two dinners a week instead of one
因为你们无法共处一室
because you can't be in the same room.
家人与生意不能搅在一起
Family and business doesn't mix.
你们总归是爱干嘛干嘛 我操个什么心
Ah, you're gonna do whatever you want. Why do I bother?
他说的对吗
Is he right?
你知道爸这个人 他是个悲观主义者
Y-you know dad. I mean, he's a pessimist.
我想我们能买下那房子
I want us to get that house.
真的 但我不想大家吵架
I do. But I don't want us to fight.
我们不会吵架的
We're not gonna fight.
当然不会了
Of course not.
可能吧
Probably.
不知道 我们会吵吗
I don't know. Will we?
也许我们可以先缓缓 好好考虑下
Maybe we just take a beat and think about it.
是 这样也没坏处
Yeah. I-I guess that couldn't hurt.
是的
Yeah.
你们是我们的至亲
You guys mean the world to us.
我可不想因为一栋房子和你们闹翻
I don't want to jeopardize that over a house.
-我们也这样觉得 -我知道
- We feel the same way. - I know.
-我只想说我知道我们会做得很好 -喂
- I just wanna say I know we'd do a good job, though. - Hello?
-我觉得 -布鲁克太太 卖房子那位
- And I feel so-- - It's Mrs. Brooks, the lady with the house.
您能来电真是太好了
Actually, it's good that you called.
什么
What?
什么事
What happened?
吉尔·索普刚刚给她出价了
Gil Thorpe just made her an offer.
-我们买了 -我们买了一栋房子
- We did it! - We bought a house.
肯定会非常棒
It's gonna be... great!
会出错吗 不可能
What could go wrong? Nothing.
有时候我不太理解人类
Sometimes I don't understand people.
他们因为最傻的原因做出疯狂的事
They do crazy things for the dumbest reasons.
我会上场 尽全力击球
I'm going to march out there and swing as hard as I can.
如果那些体育电影拍的是真的
And if every sports movie is correct,
我会奋力击中球
I'm going to smack that ball,
我跑上垒时大家会高呼我的名字
and everyone will chant my name as I round the bases.
顺便问下
By the way,
总是逆时针方向跑 还是我可以自己选
it is always counterclockwise, or do I get to choose?
怎样都没关系啦
I don't think it's gonna matter.
他们说服自己无论怎样都会有好结果
They convince themselves it'll all work out...
请各位起立唱国歌
Please rise for the national anthem.
我要让你知道谁唱得好
I'm gonna show you who can sing.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.
真是一场灾难
Oh, this is gonna be rough.
他们会无视所有相反的证据
Despite all the evidence to the contrary.
啊 你可看见
Oh say can you see?
透过一线曙光
By the dawn's early light?
我想也不算太差吧
Which I guess isn't so bad.
火炮闪闪发光
And the rocket's red glare!
我只想说
All I'm saying is,
上帝保佑你的歌声不要遗传你妈
I hope to god you don't have your mother's singing voice.
但是老天 我希望你遗传到她的自信
But, man, I hope you get her self-confidence.
快睡吧
Try to get some sleep.
我们明早再聊
I'll talk to you in the morning.
二人出局 第六局下半 四分平手
2 outs, bottom of the sixth. Tied at 4.
重要时刻来了 伙计们
This is it, folks.
成败在此一击
The whole game comes down to this.
曼尼·迪尔加多 三击全不中
Manny Delgado 0 for 3 on the day.
歌洛莉亚 你怎么看
Gloria, your thoughts?
我认为他会击出全垒打
I think he's going to hit the home run.
求你了 上帝保佑
Please, god, give me one.
曼尼 站直了
Manny, stand up straight!
膝盖弯曲
But bend your knees.
马步扎稳了
Widen your stance!
拜托你们让我...
Would you please let me just--
快跑垒
Take your base!
-你成功了 曼尼 -我成功了吗
- You did it! You got it, Manny! - I did it?
错了 不是那边 跑这边
No, no, no, no! Not that way! Go this way!
我操个什么心 反正他爱干嘛就会干嘛
Oh, why do I bother? He's gonna do what he wants.
曼尼 曼尼 曼尼
Manny! Manny! Manny!